[
  {
        "question": "A Skeleton wearing pink slippers and a blue hoodie and some basketball shorts walks up to you and reaches out to shake your hand. What do you do?",
        "choice1":"Turn around and start running",
        "choice2": "Pinch yourself",
        "choice3":"Turn around and shake his hand",
        "choice4":"comic sans ms?",
        "answer":"3" 
    },
    {
        
        "question":"You're questioned for being kinda sus. What do you say?",
        "choice1":"Nou",
        "choice2":"How can I be the impostor if you have the knife?",
        "choice3":"What? I was scanning in medbay!",
        "choice4":"à¶ž AMOGUS",
        "answer":4
    },
    {
        "question":"Kris, GET THE BANANA",
        "choice1":"What? Doesn't that make you spin?",
        "choice2":"+50 Points",
        "choice3":"Potassium.",
        "choice4":"Bork. ",
        "answer":3
    },
    {
        "question":"If you look up Super Mario Brothers in google, and you click on the question box, what happens?",
        "choice1":"A coin pops out.",
        "choice2":"A mushroom pops out.",
        "choice3":"A star pops out.",
        "choice4":"Yoshi pops out.",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question":"What virus happened in 2020?",
        "choice1":"Bonzi Buddy",
        "choice2":"Coronavirus",
        "choice3":"Memz",
        "choice4":"ILOVEYOU Email Chain",
        "answer":2
    },
    {
        "question":"What do you do after cleaning your brush?",
        "choice1":"Dry it off",
        "choice2":"Dip in the paint and go at it",
        "choice3":"Beat the devil out of it",
        "choice4":"Cry because you're out of paint..",
        "answer":3
    },
    {
        "question":"Webkinz has you redeem what kind of toy into their online game?",
        "choice1":"Cars",
        "choice2":"Trains",
        "choice3":"Pets",
        "choice4":"People",
        "answer":3
    },
    {
        "question":"Oh you're approaching me?",
        "choice1":"I don't get it...",
        "choice2":"Well yea, because I can't beat the crap out of you without getting any closer",
        "choice3":"Who are you?",
        "choice4":"okay...?",
        "answer":2
    },
    {
        "question":"UNDERTALE was made by 1 Guy, named Toby Fox, classifying it as a...",
        "choice1":"Indie Game",
        "choice2":"Nintendo Game",
        "choice3":"Fox Game",
        "choice4":"None of the Above",
        "answer":1
    },
    {
        "question":"Super Smash Brothers is a game featuring which company of games?",
        "choice1":"Microsoft",
        "choice2":"Sony",
        "choice3":"Nintendo",
        "choice4":"Mac",
        "answer":3
    }
]
